<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>All Posts - DataCarePh</title><link>https://www.datacareph.com/blog/posts/</link><description>All Posts | DataCarePh</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>Research, News, and Blog - DataCarePh</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 00:45:08 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.datacareph.com/blog/posts/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>WordPress Vulnerability Scanner: Protect Your Website from Malware</title><link>https://www.datacareph.com/blog/posts/wordpress-vulnerability-scanner-protect-your-website-from-malware/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 22:54:48 +0800</pubDate><author>Researcher</author><guid>https://www.datacareph.com/blog/posts/wordpress-vulnerability-scanner-protect-your-website-from-malware/</guid><description><![CDATA[<div class="featured-image">
                <img src="/blog/posts/src/default.png" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
            </div>Woo Link WordPress is one of the most popular content management systems, powering millions of websites worldwide. However, its popularity also makes it a prime target for hackers and malware attacks. To ensure the security of your WordPress site, it&rsquo;s crucial to regularly scan it for vulnerabilities and malware. In this article, we will discuss the importance of using a WordPress vulnerability scanner and provide guidance on running malware scans effectively.]]></description></item><item><title>Custom Add to Cart Button and Ajax Request in WooCommerce and WordPress Store</title><link>https://www.datacareph.com/blog/posts/custom-add-to-cart-button-and-ajax-request-in-woocommerce-and-wordpress-store/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 02:21:25 +0800</pubDate><author>wpdev</author><guid>https://www.datacareph.com/blog/posts/custom-add-to-cart-button-and-ajax-request-in-woocommerce-and-wordpress-store/</guid><description><![CDATA[<div class="featured-image">
                <img src="/blog/posts/img/woocommerce-add-to-cart.png" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
            </div>Creating a Custom Add to Cart Button using Ajax Request for a Seamless Checkout Experience in WooCommerce and WordPress Simple HTML and JS Approach Here&rsquo;s the solution below:
HTML Code &lt;button id=&#34;hi-add-button&#34; class=&#34;hi-add-button&#34; data-button-add=&#34;true&#34;&gt;ADD TO CART&lt;/button&gt; JQuery Code jQuery(document).ready(function($) { // Ajax Starts // Manually replace using your actual product ID const hi_products_group = [ { product_id: 242, quantity: 2 }, // Product 1 { product_id: 265, quantity: 1 }, // Product 2 // You can add more here.]]></description></item><item><title>Post's Assets Index</title><link>https://www.datacareph.com/blog/posts/src/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 00:45:08 +0800</pubDate><author>img</author><guid>https://www.datacareph.com/blog/posts/src/</guid><description>&lt;div class="featured-image">
&lt;img src="/blog/posts/img/post-default.jpg" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
&lt;/div>Index page for img folder</description></item><item><title>Redirect Non-WWW to WWW using Cloudflare as Clean Solution For Traefik: Step-by-Step Guide.</title><link>https://www.datacareph.com/blog/posts/redirects-non-www-to-www-using-cloudflare/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 08:44:35 +0000</pubDate><author>researchcare</author><guid>https://www.datacareph.com/blog/posts/redirects-non-www-to-www-using-cloudflare/</guid><description><![CDATA[<hr>
<p>You can find many instructions online on how to redirect from Non-WWW to WWW like Google search does. However, at the time of writing this, I couldn&rsquo;t find any that worked.  Particularly configuring Traefik as Proxy Server and Nginx as Web Server.</p>]]></description></item><item><title>Auto Generating Backup Files for your Linux Server</title><link>https://www.datacareph.com/blog/posts/automatically-backup-files-your-server-files/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 11:57:40 +0800</pubDate><author>venven</author><guid>https://www.datacareph.com/blog/posts/automatically-backup-files-your-server-files/</guid><description>source image: pexel.com
When doing computer work, clicking “save” is necessary to either literally or not literally save your job. This content is helpful when you are working on the Linux Operating System (OS), especially running a server. Automatically backing up your server can cost you money on a monthly basis and, of course, can save your business.
Just imagine how much of your time and effort goes to waste when you forget or have the tardiness to just press ctrl + s on your office application.</description></item><item><title>Breach Threat! Someone Can Reveal Your Saved Password from the Browser</title><link>https://www.datacareph.com/blog/posts/breach-threat-someone-can-peek-your-saved-password-from-the-browser/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 11:57:40 +0800</pubDate><author>venven</author><guid>https://www.datacareph.com/blog/posts/breach-threat-someone-can-peek-your-saved-password-from-the-browser/</guid><description>Data can be Breach We may be unaware of what’s really going on when we use our devices to access the internet. Well, this content will make you aware of what you should do when you use your favorite browser to access the internet. Hackers are eagerly pestering us to get our sensitive information, such as user credentials, passwords, credit card information, and the like.
Specifically, this information is limited to Mozilla Firefox and Google Chrome browsers, yet it may be similar to your favorite browser too.</description></item></channel></rss>