<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Abouts on DataCarePh</title><link>https://www.datacareph.com/blog/about/</link><description>Recent content in Abouts on DataCarePh</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>Research, News, and Blog - DataCarePh</copyright><lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 11:04:49 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.datacareph.com/blog/about/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Privacy Policy</title><link>https://www.datacareph.com/blog/about/privacy-policy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 11:04:49 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.datacareph.com/blog/about/privacy-policy/</guid><description>This Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, stored, retained, protected, and shared when you visit or make a purchase from DataCarePh.com (the “Site”).
At DataCarePh, we respect your privacy and recognize your rights to privacy. We are committed to protecting the personal information that you provide to us. We comply with the fundamental principles of privacy as required by Data Protection Laws, such as, but not limited to, Republic Act No.</description></item><item><title>About Us</title><link>https://www.datacareph.com/blog/about/us/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2019 11:04:49 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.datacareph.com/blog/about/us/</guid><description>Who are we? We are a group of people who are enthusiast in doing research and technical writing in the field of software development, data analysis, cyber security, and cloud technology based in Iloilo, Philippines.
Our Mission To make people aware on what’s going in their devices on the accessing the internet.
Our Vision To build an automation software to audit a particular application for safety usage.
Someone is watching you right now!</description></item><item><title>We Care</title><link>https://www.datacareph.com/blog/about/we-care/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2016 11:04:49 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://www.datacareph.com/blog/about/we-care/</guid><description>Someone is watching you right now! So what’s the catch? Have you fallen victim to this apparent click bait? Or does this concern you?
Who you’d be? When you are using a device to connect to the internet, this topic must concern you and be something to be wary of. Have you heard of the recent internet fraud? Phishing attack? Identity theft? Are you a victim? Yes? Or something you’re not aware of?</description></item></channel></rss>